Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Subject Files, Series VI.
  - Meat and Food-Prices-Spreads-Consumers IV, 1970-1971 (Box 440, Folders 28-31)
  - Meat and Food-Prices-Spreads-Consumers V, 1971-1973 (Box 440, Folder 32)
  - Meat and Food-Prices-Spreads-Consumers VI, 1973-1977 (Box 440, Folder 33)
  - Meat and Food-Prices-Spreads-Consumers VII, 1973-1977 (Box 440, Folder 34)
  - Meat and Food-Prices and Spreads-Market Spread Data and Statistics I, 1971-1977 (Box 441, Folders 1-3)
  - Meat and Food-Prices and Spreads-Market Spread Data and Statistics II, 1975-1977 (Box 441, Folders 4-7)
  - Medicated Feeds, 1981 (Box 441, Folder 8)
  - Residue Avoidance Program 1982 (Box 441, Folder 9)
  - Scabies, 1980-1982 (Box 441, Folder 10)
  - School Lunch, 1982 (Box 441, Folder 11)
  - Screw Worm, 1981 (Box 441, Folder 12)
  - Swift Fresh Meats Company, 1973-1976 (Box 441, Folder 13)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1982 (Box 441, Folder 14)
  - Tanners’ Council of America Inc., 1975 (Box 441, Folder 15)
  - Tenderizing, 1977-1980 (Box 441, Folder 16)
  - Texas Tech News, 1982-1983 (Box 441, Folder 17)
  - Timely Marketing Project, 1981-1982 (Box 441, Folder 18)
  - Trade Negotiation Information Service, 1975-1977 (Box 441, Folder 19)
  - Training Programs, 1975 (Box 441, Folder 20)
  - 2, 4, 5-T, circa 1979 (Box 441, Folder 21)
  - 1980 Congressional Campaigns (Box 441, Folder 22)
  - National Wildlife Refuges, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 23)
  - OSHA, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 24)
  - 160 Acre Limit, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 25)
  - NISARC, 1979 (Box 441, Folder 26)
  - PCB’s, 1980 (Box 441, Folders 27-28)
  - Off-Road Vehicles, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 29)
  - Odor Pollution, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 30)
  - OSHA, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 31)
  - Nutritional Labeling, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 32)
  - Nutrition, 1980 (Box 441, Folder 33)
  - National Trails, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - National Wool Growers Association, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Natural Gas, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Natural Diversity, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - New Zealand, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Nitrites, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 6)
  - Nutritionists, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 7)
  - Nutrition, 1980s (Box 442, Folders 8-11)
  - MBPXL, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 12)
  - Manure-Use/Value, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 13)
  - Market Research, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 14)
  - Market Structure, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 15)
  - Marketing, 1984 (Box 442, Folder 16)
  - Marketing Systems, 1983 (Box 442, Folder 17)
  - Marketing Seminar, 1976 (Box 442, Folder 18)
  - Meat Consumption, 1983 (Box 442, Folder 19)
  - Meat Demand, 1983 (Box 442, Folder 20)
  - Meat-Diet (1), 1978 (Box 443, Folder 1)
  - Meat-Diet (2), 1978 (Box 443, Folder 2)
  - Meat-Diet (3), 1978 (Box 443, Folder 3)
  - Michieli, Ron, Sassafras Lodge A, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Railroads, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 5)
  - Calgary Meetings, 1979 (Box 443, Folder 6)
  - Animal Health Institute, 1979 (Box 443, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations, 1979 (Box 443, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii, 1981 (Box 443, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Agricultural Service, 1980 (Box 443, Folder 10)
  - 1985 Farm Bill, 1985-1986 (Box 443, Folder 11)
  - Brucellosis, 1975 (Box 443, Folder 12)
  - Antibiotics, 1975 (Box 443, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Trade Committee, 1978 (Box 443, Folder 14)
  - AM. Veterinary Service, 1979 (Box 443, Folder 15)
  - Antibiotics, 1979 (Box 443, Folder 16)
  - Grades, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 17)
  - Grain Embargo, 1980 (Box 443, Folder 18)
  - Grain Feeding, 1980 (Box 443, Folder 19)
  - Grain Feeding-Issue, 1980 (Box 443, Folder 20)
  - Grazing Fees, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 21)
  - Grazing-Public Lands, 1976 (Box 443, Folder 22)
  - Great Western Beef Expo, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 23)
  - Ground Beef, 1978 (Box 443, Folder 24)
  - Beef Futures, 1975, undated (Box 443, Folder 25)
  - Government Food Purchases, 1978-1981 (Box 443, Folder 26)
  - 2, 4, 5-T, 1983-1984 (Box 443, Folders 27-29)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Right to Work Committee IX, 1977 (Box 444, Folder 1)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Right to Work Committee VIII, 1976 (Box 444, Folder 2)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Right to Work Committee VII, 1976 (Box 444, Folder 3)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Right to Work Committee VI, 1975 (Box 444, Folder 4)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Right to Work Committee V, 1974 (Box 444, Folder 5)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Right to Work Committee IV, 1974 (Box 444, Folder 6)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Secondary Boycotts-Food, 1975 (Box 444, Folder 7)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Labor Unions and Antitrust, 1975 (Box 444, Folder 8)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-IBP Strike and Secondary Boycotts, 1977 (Box 444, Folder 9)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Productivity-Other Restraints in Trade, 1976 (Box 444, Folder 10)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Politician Contributions-Labor Unions, 1977 (Box 444, Folder 11)
  - Farm (Collective) Bargaining-General Info-Material-Correspondence I, 1973 (Box 444, Folder 12)
  - Farm (Collective) Bargaining-Testimony-General Info I, 1972 (Box 444, Folder 13)
  - Farm (Collective) Bargaining-Testimony-General Info II, 1971 (Box 444, Folder 14)
  - Farm (Collective) Bargaining-Testimony-General Info III, 1971 (Box 444, Folder 15)
  - Farm (Collective) Bargaining-Testimony-General Info I, 1971 (Box 444, Folder 16)
  - Farm Bargaining-Michigan, 1972 (Box 444, Folder 17)
  - Law-Regulations and Information, Capper-Volstead Act, undated (Box 444, Folder 18)
  - Farm (Collective) Bargaining-General Info-Material, 1966-1970 (Box 444, Folder 19)
  - Senate-Farm Bargaining Legislation-General, 1968-1969 (Box 444, Folder 20)
  - 90th Congress-Farm Bargaining-Agricultural Practices Act-1967 (Box 444, Folder 21)
  - Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act, undated (Box 444, Folder 22)
  - Meat Imports-Wild Animals, undated (Box 444, Folder 23)
  - Child Nutrition and School Lunch Acts, undated (Box 444, Folder 24)
  - Transportation, 1977 (Box 445, Folder 1)
  - Transportation-Railroad Claims against Shippers, 1974 (Box 445, Folder 2)
  - Transportation-Freight Rate Changes-Hearings-ICC, 1970 (Box 445, Folder 3)
  - Transportation-Railroad Mergers, 1962 (Box 445, Folder 4)
  - Transportation-Freight Rate Changes-Hearings-ICC-Statements, 1970, 1972 (Box 445, Folders 5-6)
  - Transportation-Reduction Rail Rates from Midwest II, 1964 (Box 445, Folder 7)
  - Transportation-Info-Reduction Rail Rates from Midwest, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 8)
  - Transportation-Uniform Rail Car Charges II, 1969 (Box 445, Folder 9)
  - Transportation-Uniform Rail Car Charges I, 1968 (Box 445, Folder 10)
  - Transportation-Follow-Lot Rules-Rails-Livestock, 1967 (Box 445, Folder 11)
  - Transportation-Carrier Proposals-Rails-General, 1970 (Box 445, Folder 12)
  - Transportation-Fuel and Energy-Info and Material, 1973 (Box 445, Folder 13)
  - Transportation-Federal Use Tax-Trucks, 1972 (Box 445, Folder 14)
  - Transportation-Regulations-Motor Carrier Safety, 1971 (Box 445, Folder 15)
  - Transportation-Regulations and Info-Livestock Trucks, 1975 (Box 445, Folder 16)
  - Transportation-Info-Hearings-Truck Size and Weight, 1975 (Box 445, Folder 17)
  - Transportation-Info-Legislative Options, 1973 (Box 445, Folder 18)
  - Transportation-Info-Hearings-Cancel Minimum Rate Regulation, 1963 (Box 445, Folder 19)
  - Transportation-Transportation and Improvement Act, 1974 (Box 445, Folder 20)
  - Transportation-Bills to Amend-Interstate Commerce Act, 1968 (Box 445, Folder 21)
  - Transportation-General Correspondence, and Information-Department of Transportation, 1975 (Box 445, Folder 22)
  - Transportation, 1974 (Box 445, Folder 23)
  - Direct Selling, 1963 (Box 445, Folder 24)
  - Auction Markets, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 25)
  - Extension of Marketing Week, Terminals, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 26)
  - Regular and Orderly Marketing, Terminals, 1963 (Box 445, Folder 27)
  - Selling Livestock, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 28)
  - Marketing Changes, Improvement, Progress, Livestock Marketing, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 29)
  - Terminals-Private Treaty and Auctions, 1969 (Box 445, Folder 30)
  - Order Buyers, 1964 (Box 445, Folder 31)
  - Hog Buying-Proposal, Wilson and Co., 1966 (Box 445, Folder 32)
  - Purchasing Livestock, undated (Box 445, Folder 33)
  - Private Branding, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 34)
  - Livestock Marketing-Weights, 1966 (Box 445, Folder 35)
  - General Marketing Information, 1968 (Box 445, Folder 36)
  - N-1963 National Marketing Service Workshop (Box 445, Folder 37)
  - International Meat Research Conference, 1980 (Box 445, Folders 38-39)
  - Food and Nutrition Board Hearings, 1980 (Box 446, Folders 1-2)
  - American Meat Institute-SuperJet ’81: A Meat Information Conference, 1981 (Box 446, Folder 3)
  - Committee Chairmen and V-Chairmen Meeting, 1979 (Box 446, Folder 4)
  - National Cancer Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 446, Folder 5)
  - Federal Meat Inspection-Regulations-General-Facilities, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 6)
  - Federal Meat Inspection-Regulations-Product Standards, Labeling, Etc., 1969, 1977 (Box 446, Folders 7-8)
  - Federal Meat Inspection-Regulations-Animal Identification, 1976 (Box 446, Folder 9)
  - Meat Inspection-Poultry Products Inspection, 1971 (Box 446, Folder 10)
  - Meat Inspection-Federally Inspected Establishments, Lists and Applications, 1968 (Box 446, Folder 11)
  - Irradiation-Meat, 1967 (Box 446, Folder 12)
  - Meat-Trade in Unsanitary, 1966 (Box 446, Folder 13)
  - Meat Inspection-Exports, 1966 (Box 446, Folder 14)
  - Meat Inspection-Official Stamps and Labels, 1973 (Box 446, Folder 15)
  - Pork Quality Improvement, 1966 (Box 446, Folder 16)
  - Meat Inspection Service, Transfer from ARS, 1965 (Box 446, Folder 17)
  - Costs of Meat Inspection, Transfer to Industry, 1966 (Box 446, Folder 18)
  - Meat Inspection-State Programs, 1973 (Box 446, Folder 19)
  - Meat Inspection-Federal Meat Inspection-Imports, 1971 (Box 446, Folder 20)
  - Federal Meat Inspection-Imports, 1965-1970 (Box 446, Folder 21)
  - Federal Meat Inspection-Imported Meat and Meat Products, Inspection, Regulations, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 22)
  - Marketing and Consumer Services, School Lunch Program, 1975 (Box 446, Folder 23)
  - Marketing and Consumer Services, Food Stamp Program-Regulations, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 24)
  - Consumer Marketing Services, USDA-Proposal and Organization, 1975 (Box 446, Folder 25)
  - Consumer and Marketing Service, Livestock Division-General, 1970 (Box 446, Folder 26)
  - USDA Matching Funds Projects, Consumer and Marketing Service, 1976 (Box 446, Folder 27)
  - Food Assistance, 1976-1977 (Box 446, Folders 28-29)
  - Consumer and Marketing Service, USDA Meat Purchases-Sec. 32 Funds, 1971 (Box 446, Folder 30)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture, Organization and Administration-Department of Labor, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 31)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-General Correspondence and Information-Department of Labor, 1974 (Box 446, Folder 32)
  - Labor, Miscellaneous Information, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 33)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Correspondence and Information-Agriculture Labor Rel. Act, 1973 (Box 447, Folder 1)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-National Labor Rel. Act, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 2)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Bills-Fair Labor Standards Act, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 3)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Common Site Picketing Bills, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 4)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Correspondence, and Information-Fair Labor Standards Act, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 5)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Correspondence, and Information-Sec. 14(b)-Right to Work, 1965, 1977 (Box 447, Folders 6-7)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-IBP Strike, 1973-1974 (Box 447, Folder 8)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Regulations, 1975 (Box 447, Folder 9)
  - Labor-Strikes, 1982 (Box 447, Folder 10)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Labor Strikes-Various Plants, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 11)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Collective Bargaining Industry Fact Sheets, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 12)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-MBPXL Strike, 1976 (Box 447, Folder 13)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Labor Negotiations, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 14)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Farm Labor Research Committee, 1982 (Box 447, Folder 15)
  - Labor-Industry and Agriculture-Labor Union Organization, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 16)
  - Labor-National Right to Work Committee X, 1982 (Box 447, Folder 17)
  - Marketing, 1970s-1980s (Box 447, Folders 18-19)
  - Marketing, 1970s-1980s (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Meat Demand, 1982 (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Meat Extenders, 1982 (Box 448, Folder 3)
  - The Meat Sheet, 1974-1978 (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Beef Substitutes, 1971, 1974 (Box 448, Folder 5)
  - Metric System, 1975-1976 (Box 448, Folder 6)
  - New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1976 (Box 448, Folder 7)
  - National Restaurant Association, 1981 (Box 448, Folder 8)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association Resolutions, 1972-1977 (Box 448, Folder 9)
  - National Resources Defense Council vs. Morton, 1974-1975 (Box 448, Folders 10-11)
  - Labeling Meat-Oregon Case, 1968 (Box 448, Folder 12)
  - Labeling Meat-Tennessee Case, 1965 (Box 448, Folder 13)
  - Food and Meat Substitutes-Enforcement of Regulations, Standards, Identity Labeling, 1976 (Box 448, Folder 14)
  - Food and Meat Substitutes-Regulations-Standards, Identity, and Labeling, 1966 (Box 448, Folder 15)
  - Food and Meat Substitutes-Regulations-Food Additives, 1973 (Box 448, Folder 16)
  - Food and Meat Substitutes-Standards-Identity-Labeling, General Information II, 1977 (Box 448, Folder 17)
  - Food and Meat Substitutes-Standards-Identity-Labeling, General Information I, 1971 (Box 448, Folder 18)
  - Food and Meat Substitutes-Meat Substitutes-Examples, Description, 1973 (Box 448, Folder 19)
  - Consumer Affairs-Consumer Protection Legislation IV, 1977 (Box 448, Folders 20-21)
  - Consumer Affairs-Consumer Protection Legislation III, 1977 (Box 448, Folder 22)
  - Consumer Affairs-Consumer Protection Legislation II, 1974 (Box 448, Folder 23)
  - Consumer Affairs-Consumer Protection Legislation I, 1973 (Box 448, Folder 24)
  - Consumer Affairs-Office of Consumer Affairs-White House, 1975 (Box 448, Folder 25)
  - Consumer Affairs-Consumerism Material, 1974 (Box 448, Folder 26)
  - Consumer Affairs-Dietary Issues and Nutrition III, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Consumer Affairs-Dietary Issues and Nutrition II, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Consumer Affairs-Dietary Issues and Nutrition I, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Food Stamps-Bills, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 4)
  - Food Stamps, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 5)
  - Marketing and Consumer Services-Food Stamp Act, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Marketing and Consumer Services-Food Stamp Program II, 1977 (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Marketing and Consumer Services-Food Stamp Program I, 1975 (Box 449, Folder 8)
  - Renewable Resources, 1980 (Box 449, Folder 9)
  - Cattle Cycles, 1976-1982 (Box 449, Folders 10-16)
  - Modeling Agriculture for Policy Analysis in the 1980s, 1981 (Box 449, Folders 17-18)
  - National Industry-State Agriculture Research Council, 1976-1981 (Box 449, Folder 19)
  - Cement Kiln Dust, 1977-1981 (Box 449, Folder 20)
  - Bluetongue, 1966-1980 (Box 449, Folder 21)
  - Brucellosis, 1977-1980 (Box 449, Folders 22-26)
  - Bovine Respiratory Disease, 1976-1979 (Box 449, Folder 27)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1971-1981 (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Imports, 1970-1971 (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Identification of Livestock, 1978-1981 (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture-Animal and Plant Health Identification Service, 1978-1981 (Box 450, Folder 4)
  - Imports, 1975-1976 (Box 450, Folders 5-9)
  - Tariff Commission-Imports, 1960 (Box 450, Folder 10)
  - Joint ANCA-NWGA Study on Imports, 1959 (Box 450, Folder 11)
  - Australian 1958 Import Situation (Box 450, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles-San Francisco Imports, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 13)
  - Trade Agreements Extension Act, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 14)
  - Reciprocal Trade Agreements, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 15)
  - News Items, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 16)
  - Other Industries, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 17)
  - Statements, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 18)
  - Tariff Revision, 1954 (Box 450, Folder 19)
  - Production Figures, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 20)
  - Trade Agreements, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Tariff Commission-Committee for Reciprocity Information, Editorial, 1946 (Box 450, Folder 22)
  - Import Figures, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 23)
  - Mexican Imports, 1949 (Box 450, Folder 24)
  - Tariff Rates, undated (Box 450, Folder 25)
  - Import Figures, 1957 (Box 450, Folder 26)
  - Tariff Commission, 1956 (Box 450, Folder 27)
  - Argentine Meat, 1951 (Box 450, Folder 28)
  - Argentine Sanitary Convention, 1935 (Box 450, Folder 29)
  - Foot and Mouth Disease, 1940s-1950s, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 30)
  - Exports, 1956 (Box 450, Folder 31)
  - International Trade Organization, 1947, 1950 (Box 450, Folder 32)
  - Reciprocal Trade, 1953 (Box 450, Folder 33)
  - Quotas, 1948 (Box 450, Folder 34)
  - Tariff Rates, 1946 (Box 450, Folder 35)
  - Tariffs, 1947-1948 (Box 450, Folder 36)
  - Extension of 1955, GATT, 1956 (Box 450, Folder 37)
  - Tariff, 1953 (Box 450, Folder 38)
  - Reciprocal Trade, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 39)
  - Controls-Restrictions-Licenses-Quotas, 1958 (Box 450, Folder 40)
  - Wayne, John, 1972 (Box 450, Folder 41)
  - Management Study, 1967 (Box 450, Folder 42)
  - 1961 Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference (Box 450, Folder 43)
  - 1963 Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference (Box 450, Folders 44-45)
  - 1965 Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference (Box 451, Folder 1)
  - 1967 Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference, 1966-1967 (Box 451, Folders 2-6)
  - Imports, 1964-1972, undated (Box 451, Folders 7-12)
  - Brucellosis, 1967 (Box 451, Folder 13)
  - Imports, Geneva, 1963-1967 (Box 451, Folder 14)
  - Import Legislation, 1964-1971 (Box 451, Folders 15-24)
  - Import Legislation, 1963-1968, undated (Box 452, Folders 1-3)
  - Imports-S. 557, 1963 (Box 452, Folder 4)
  - Imports-Trade and Tariff Report, undated (Box 452, Folder 5)
  - Imports-Governors Conference, 1963 (Box 452, Folder 6)
  - Import Conference, 1964 (Box 452, Folder 7)
  - Australia-New Zealand Import Conference, 1963 (Box 452, Folder 8)
  - Imports-Geneva Trade Talks, 1963 (Box 452, Folder 9)
  - Imports #1, #2, #3, #4, 1963 (Box 452, Folders 10-13)
  - Imports-General, 1960 (Box 452, Folder 14)
  - Imports, 1963 (Box 452, Folder 15)
  - Imports, 1960 (Box 453, Folder 1)
  - President’s European Beef Mission, 1965 (Box 453, Folder 2)
  - House Agriculture Committee, 1965 (Box 453, Folder 3)
  - Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 453, Folder 4)
  - United Livestock Feeders Association, 1964 (Box 453, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Livestock Sanitary Association, 1965 (Box 453, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Treasury Dept., 1964 (Box 453, Folder 7)
  - Reapportionment, 1965 (Box 453, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 9)
  - Right to Work, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Agriculture, 1972 (Box 453, Folder 11)
  - Sharon, Pierson, and Semes, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 12)
  - Sisk Bill, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 13)
  - Starlings, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 14)
  - Statistics Report, Tanners Council, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 15)
  - Swift Fresh Meats Co., 1971 (Box 453, Folder 16)
  - Tax, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 17)
  - Telephone File, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 18)
  - Society for Range Management, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 19)
  - USAHA, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Beef Breeds Council, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 21)
  - USDA-Beef Cattle Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 22)
  - USDA-General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 23)
  - Foot and Mouth Disease, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 24)
  - USDA-Producer Industry Advisory Committee on Grains, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 25)
  - USDA-Advisory Council on Child Nutrition, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 26)
  - Ag-Research, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 27)
  - USDA-Consumer and Marketing, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 28)
  - USDA-Animal Research Center, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 29)
  - USDA-Food and Drug Administration, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 30)
  - USDA-FAS, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 31)
  - USDA-Forest Service, 1972 (Box 453, Folder 32)
  - USDA-Packers and Stockyards Act, 1972 (Box 453, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Department of Health, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 34)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 35)
  - Van Dusen, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 36)
  - “VIP” Reservations, 1969 (Box 453, Folder 37)
  - White House Conference on Nutrition, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 38)
  - White House Correspondence, 1971 (Box 453, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural Chemicals, 1970 (Box 453, Folder 40)
  - Iowa Beef Processors, 1971 (Box 454, Folder 1)
  - American Agricultural Editors Association, 1956, 1960-1968, undated (Box 454, Folders 2-6)
  - American Association of Agricultural College Editors, 1960-1962 (Box 454, Folders 7-8)
  - American Forestry Association, 1963-1968, undated (Box 454, Folders 9-10)
  - American Humane Association (Humane Society), Certificate of Appointment for Charles W. McMillan, 1965 (Box 454, Folder 11)
  - American Humane Association (Humane Society), 1963-1969, undated (Box 454, Folders 12-15)
  - American National Livestock Auction Association, 1955-1957 (Box 454, Folders 16-17)
  - American National Livestock Association, 1957 (Box 454, Folder 18)
  - American Quarter Horse Association, 1958-1963 (Box 454, Folder 19)
  - American Society of Animal Science, 1968 (Box 454, Folder 20)
  - American Society of Range Management, 1964-1968 (Box 454, Folders 21-22)
  - American Stockyards Association, 1964-1966, undated (Box 454, Folders 23-25)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1962-1968 (Box 454, Folders 26-27)
  - Beef Improvement Association, 1967-1968 (Box 454, Folders 28-33)
  - Colorado-Nebraska Lamb Feeders’ Association, 1958 (Box 454, Folder 34)
  - Colorado Wool Growers’ Association, 1958-1968 (Box 454, Folder 35)
  - Idaho Wool Growers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 454, Folder 36)
  - International Association of Game, Fish, and Conservation Commissioners, 1966 (Box 454, Folder 37)
  - Livestock Auction Markets Association, 1958-1969 (Box 454, Folders 38-39)
  - Montana Wool Growers Association, 1959-1963 (Box 454, Folder 40)
  - National Association of Animal Breeders, 1966-1967 (Box 454, Folders 41-42)
  - Nebraska Livestock Feeders Association, 1980-1987 (Box 454, Folder 43)
  - Texas Sheep and Goat Raisers Association, 1958-1963 (Box 454, Folder 44)
  - Thoroughbred Owners and Breeders Association, 1958-1964 (Box 454, Folder 45)
  - U.S. Livestock Sanitary Association, 1967-1968 (Box 454, Folders 46-47)
  - Utah Wool Growers Association, 1959-1963 (Box 454, Folder 48)
  - Washington Wool Growers Association, 1958-1962 (Box 454, Folder 49)
  - Western States Cattle Association’s Organization, 1960 (Box 454, Folder 50)
  - Western Stock Growers Association, 1968-1969 (Box 454, Folder 51)
  - Wyoming Wool Growers Association, 1958-1962 (Box 454, Folder 52)
  - American Humane Association (Humane Society), 1960-1964 (Box 454, Folder 53)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua, 1972 (Box 454, Folder 54)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua-Arizona, 1971-1972 (Box 454, Folder 55)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua-California, 1971-1972 (Box 454, Folder 56)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua-Chautauqua Memo to ANCA Board of Directors, 1972 (Box 454, Folder 57)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua, Chautauqua Trips, 1973 (Box 454, Folder 58)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua- Chautauqua Memo to IIC Committee, Speakers, Sponsors, Arrangers, and ANCA Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 454, Folder 59)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua-East, 1973 (Box 454, Folder 60)
  - Cattlemen’s Chautauqua-Critique, 1972 (Box 454, Folder 61)